

Nihat SAFARLIBakikhanov,Baku,Azerbaijan

+994 70 897 94 77 safarlinihat@gmail.com www.nihatsafarli.com

ABOUT ME

I am Nihat Safarli, born Sheki in 1993. I started to be interested in software when I was studying for my master's degree in 2019.As a result of my research, I decided to learn C# language.In the last 3 years, I have developed myself in this field, and I have done a few projects for both learning and self-development. I also have 2 projects that I continue to do to improve myself. I have tried to learn this language down to the last detail by participating in online and offline courses, and I am trying.

LANGUAGES

- English-intermediate
- German-elementary
- Azerbaijani-native
- Turkish-native

EXPERIENCE

C# Developer, Freelance, İstanbul-Baku March 2019-Present

Manager Assistant, Shebnem Hotel, İstanbul January 2017-November 2020

Project Manager, RiskCenter Education Center, İstanbul September 2016-September 2017

Team Leader, Bazarstore MMC, Sheki September 2014 - June 2016

SKILLS

C#; Asp.Net; Asp.Net Mvc; WindowsForms; Rdlc Report; DevExpress; Entity Framework; Codefirst; DbFirst; LocalDb; Ado.Net; OOP;MsSql; LinQ; Microsoft Access Db; OOP; Git; Rest Api; Web Api; Html; Css;

Bootstrap;Flexbox;Javascript;JQuery;ReactJs;Redux;Hooks;Ajax

PROJECTS

Hospital Management System - 2019

Commercial Automation System in DevExpress - 2020 School Grading System-2020

Stock App-2021

Market Sales System(With Bar-code)-2022 Library Management System with Mvc-2022

Web Module Hotel Reservation System on DevExpress with C#-2022-present

Property Site (Web Application) with Asp.Net Mvc5-2022-present

E-Commerce Project with Asp.Net Mvc-2022-present

EDUCATION

Master-International Relations, Istanbul University, İstanbul September 2018-Present

Bachelor, Anadolu University, Eskişehir September 2021-Present

Bachelor-Geography-GPA-91.00 , Azerbaijan State Pedagogic University, Baku September 2011-June 2015

School, Sheki 11 No School, Sheki September 1999-May 2010

REFERENCES

Erman Altındağ from Apollo Hotel Systems ermanaltınd@gmail.com | +905327043313

Ünal Çakmak from Şebnem Hotel unal.cakmak@gmail.com | +905457956977

Şenlik Beyişov from Bazarstore MMC

Aydoğan Durmuş from RiskCenter Education Center info@riskcenter.edu.tr | +902122173367

CERTIFICATES-COURSES

- 1.Murat Yücedağ-C# ile Algoritma ve Programlama, TurkCell;
- 2.C# Kursu, T.C Hazine Ve Maliye Bakanlığı-BTK AKADEMİ;
- 3. Modern C# Kursu: .NET Dünyası İçin Sıfırdan Profesyonelliğe, udemy.com
- 4.C# Camp, Kodlama.Io;
- 5.Komple ASP.NET Web Geliştirme Eğitimi-udemy.com;
- 6.Her Yönüyle SQL Server-T.C Hazine Ve Maliye Bakanlığı-BTK AKADEMİ
- 7.ASP.NET MVC-udemy.com

LINKS

safarlinihat@gmail.com www.nihatsafarli.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/nihat-safarli-

235449153/

https://github.com/nihatsafarli

 $\frac{https://stackoverflow.com/users/17243388/nihat}{safarli?tab=profile}$

https://medium.com/@safarlinihat

https://www.reddit.com/user/nihatsafarli

https://www.kaggle.com/nihatsafarli

 $\underline{https://www.c\text{-}sharpcorner.com/members/nihat-}$

<u>safarli</u>

Hobbies

Reading Psychological Books; Watching Documentaries About Space and Space Technologies; Go On Nature Walks; Outdoor Activities